better.com 2019-07-18

# Privacy Policy | Better.com

**Effective Date:** 09/28/2018

We take our clients’ privacy very seriously. We understand that your privacy is important. This Privacy Policy describes how we collect and use the personal information that we collect about you on www.better.com (the "Website").

By continuing to use the Website, you agree to this Privacy Policy and the collection, use, disclosure, and storage of your personal information as described by this Privacy Policy.

### Information We Collect

When you use the Website, we may collect personal information about you, such as your name, address, Social Security number, telephone number, email address, asset information, income information, or any other information that you submit on applications or other forms made available through the Website. We collect this information when you request a rate quote, begin an application, or make an inquiry.

We may also collect personal information about you from third party sources, which we may combine with information that you provided to us or we previously collected. For example, we may receive information from a social media service about you if you use a social media account to log into the Website.

We also automatically collect certain information related to you and your activities on the Website when you visit the Website. This information includes information such as your IP address, your internet browser and operating system type, the date and time of your visit, and the website that referred you to us.

### Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

Our Website uses cookies and other tracking technologies, such as web beacons (otherwise known as pixel tags). A "cookie" is a small file placed on your computer that helps us to recognize your browser. We use both first and third-party cookies and tracking technologies on the Website. These cookies and tracking technologies may collect your personal information. We may use cookies and tracking technologies to monitor how the Website is used, customize content, serve advertisements and evaluate the effectiveness of our advertising campaigns, identify problems with the Website, improve the Website, analyze Website traffic and other analytics purposes, monitor the security of the Website, and gauge the effectiveness of our communications. Most web browsers allow you to adjust your preferences to reject cookies or to receive notifications before they are placed. If your browser is set to reject cookies, you may continue to use the Website, but some aspects of the Website may not function as intended.

### Tracking

Our first-party cookies and tracking technologies do not track users over time and across third-party websites, and therefore the Website does not respond to web browser do-not-track signals.

We also use third-party cookies to serve targeted advertisements on both the Website and on third-party websites. These cookies may track users over time and across third-party websites and services. Please note that if you opt-out of advertising cookies, you may still see our advertisements on third-party websites and services.

### How We Use Collected Information

We use personal information and anonymous information for the following purposes:

  * To complete and fulfill your loan application;
  * To respond to and fulfill your requests;
  * For our marketing efforts, such as to send you marketing communications that we believe may be of interest to you;
  * For our business purposes, such as for analysis and to develop new products and services;
  * To improve the Website and for analytics purposes; or
  * For any other purpose to which you consent.

### How We Share Personal Information

We will only share personal information with third parties as described in this Privacy Policy. We may share personal information with third parties:

  * Such as vendors who provide employment verification, degree verification, title, document import, or other necessary services;
  * Such as our Better Mortgage Corporation affiliated businesses that provide quality services or products you may be interested in;
  * For any purpose to which you expressly consent;
  * To protect our rights or the rights or safety of others; and
  * As may be required by law or regulation.

We limit the information that we send service providers, and require that our service providers only use shared personal information to perform the services requested in accordance with this Privacy Policy and have adequate security measures in place to protect any of your shared personal information.

For example, after you authorize us to verify your credit history, we send the minimal set of information needed (potentially including your social security number) to ensure we are requesting the correct record in an encrypted form to the relevant credit bureaus with the sole purpose of retrieving your credit report and associated credit history data. We would not send the same level of information to a service provider where it is not essential to perform their services.

For retrieving bank information (transactions, accounts, and other information), we use Plaid and AccountChek by FormFree as third-party service providers. Their respective privacy policies are available here: [Plaid](https://plaid.com/legal/) and [AccountChek](http://www.formfree.com/privacy/).

In the event that we enter into a corporate transaction, such as a reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer, or other disposition of all or any portion of our business, assets, or stock (including in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings), personal information that we have collected may be transferred in the course of that corporate transaction to the relevant third party purchaser, joint venture partner, merged entity, assignee or similar party.

### How We Protect Personal Information

Better Mortgage uses reasonable physical, technical, and administrative security measures to protect personal information we collect from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, or improper disclosure. For example, we use encryption technologies when transmitting information to and from the Website and with our third-party service providers. Please understand that no security technology is completely secure, and remember that when communicating with Better Mortgage, email is not a secure form of communication when transmitting sensitive or personal information.

### Links to Other Websites

The Website may contain links to third-party websites, such as social media websites. This Privacy Policy is only applicable to this Website, and Better Mortgage has no control of these third-party websites' information practices. Please be sure to review these third-party websites' privacy policies before visiting these third-party websites.

### Children's Privacy

This Website is not intended for persons under the age of 18. We do not knowingly collect, maintain, or use personal information from children under the age of 13. If we become aware that a child under the age of 13 has submitted personal information to us through the Website, we will immediately delete such information.

### Access to and Control Over Information

You may opt-out of any future marketing contacts from us at any time. You can do the following by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:

  * See what data we have about you, if any;
  * Change/correct any data we have about you;
  * Delete any information about you that we are not required by law to keep; and
  * Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

### Updates to this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to update this Privacy Policy at any time. Any changes will be immediately effective upon the posting of the updated policy. Your continued use of the Website after these updates are posted represents your consent to the terms of the new Privacy Policy. Please regularly check this Privacy Policy for any such updates.
